♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
[Emerson] I have a sighting
of Tailor AFAM.
[in English] I already have visuals.
Be alert.
[in English] What happened? Are you okay?
[Emerson groans] Pulikat! Pulikat!
[in English] This is for muscles.
Rub it on your muscle, here.
Third tree. [coughs]
Three trees, past the bridge.
[in English] Copy, copy.
[in English] We have news
about Dmitri Regalia.
[in English] He is dead.
[in English] You'll go to the funeral.
[Samir, in English] Audrey
and her daughter will be at the funeral.
[in English] You bring them
back to me untouched.
- [Samir, in English] Bring them back.
- [Emerson, in English] Mission abort.
- Huh?
- [in English] That's Audrey, right?
- [Audrey, in English] Go, go, go, go, go!
[Kurt, in English] He's chasing Mama Mary
and the Adopted Thread!
Is that Audrey?!
[Mongki] Let's go. We need to get them.
[Samir, in English]
Where do you think you are going?
[grunting and groaning]
There is a royal rumble there!
[boy] AFAM versus blond thug
versus fat vendor with a bolo!
Gavin!
[grunting and groaning]
[Kurt] Children of the Thread, let's go!
[security guard, in English] They're gone.
So, they want to kidnap her
to blackmail Atoy.
So, what does that mean? They have Atoy.
How do we find out
where Brother Atoy is now?
What if we kidnap Samir?
Let's save Atoy!
[in English] Operation Kidnap AFAM.
- [Karla] Let's go!
- [Gavin] Let's go! Let's go!
Atoy!
After you eat, don't throw away the bone.
We can still use it.
I can't be the only one eating.
[Lily] You should eat too.
You need strength.
PREVIOUSLY
[music fades]
What's new?
You failed again.
Boss, when we were tracing Olga
at the jogging park earlier,
we spotted Audrey with Gavin.
So, they're still together.
What were they doing there?
Jogging, of course. It's a jogging park.
You're being sarcastic.
Do you want me to replace you?
Don't, boss. I still have
a lot of bills to pay.
But boss, when we chased them,
suddenly, two tall mestizo guys
also tried to kidnap them.
[Mongki] We got in the middle,
of course, but…
everyone scattered.
[pensive music playing]
Looks like Atoy struck
the nerve of other people too.
That's good. That might
make our job easier.
Just don't let Gavin get dragged in.
It wasn't just those two there, boss.
Someone was protecting them.
A young man, good at fighting.
[tense music playing]
He even looks a bit like me,
if I shaved my mustache and beard.
So, I'm sure, boss,
those two won't be dealt with easily.
[music swells]
[music fades]
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[clicking]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[music swells]
[electronic blipping]
[music fades]
Hey, Ibyang?
Hey.
Ibyang, what are you doing? It's late.
Shouldn't you be asleep?
I was waiting for you, Sister Faye.
Me?
Mm-hmm.
Because I was thinking of…
a gift for Mama.
[in English] Gift? Well…
Your mom loves cupcakes.
Maybe that.
- [in English] Cupcake?
- Mmm-mm.
Oh, I don't have money to buy that.
- Sister Faye, maybe…
- What?
- Do you have money?
- Hey.
- Please lend me some.
Oh my. This kid.
Don't borrow from me
because I don't have money either.
- Oh no.
- I have an idea.
What if you give your mom
something that comes from the heart?
That's priceless.
She'll love that more.
Ah.
[Ibyang] "Tatoy, Tatoy,
even if you're not my real father,
in my heart, you're the true hero!"
[sentimental music playing]
- I know! I know, I know.
- Hmm?
I will just write her a poem!
Oh, hmm…
That's also what I gave Tatoy.
Don't you miss your Tatoy?
Don't you want to go back to him?
I miss him.
- But Mama needs me.
- Oh…
We should be together, but…
- I text him.
- Mmm?
But he doesn't reply.
Oh…
All right. Don't think about that anymore.
Here's what you should do.
Get some rest, sleep, because tomorrow,
we'll go out again.
- Do you want that?
- We'll go out again?
Yes.
But we just went out earlier.
You… You're really pesky.
Come on. Go inside.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Come on. Go inside.
You know what we'll do, right?
[in English] So, let's work
on the disguise requirements.
[Kurt] And ask right away,
so we can finalize everything
before we leave tomorrow.
- [Kurt, in English] Okay?
- [in English] Okay.
[Ame] Brother Kurt,
please message Emerson.
Tell him to also buy batteries
for our earpieces.
I'll take care of that.
I'll get the whole team new earpieces.
[pensive music playing]
That's why you're my ace.
- Right, Karla?
- [Karla] Huh?
Karla, maybe you shouldn't come.
It's dangerous.
Something… Something bad
might happen to you.
Mom, don't think negatively.
You saw it, right?
We're planning this thoroughly.
I can handle myself.
One more thing.
This is not the first time I'm joining
a mission with Brother Atoy.
I can help.
Miss Cita, don't worry.
I'll take care of Karla.
I won't let anything happen to her,
and I'll bring her home safe.
I'm nervous.
[clears throat]
Miss Cita, you can also count on me.
I'll protect Karla.
I won't abandon my friend.
[sneaky music playing]
Ouch!
- [Uno] Why? What happened?
- Oh, wow, Karla.
Your hair is so long.
It reaches up to here.
- Fix it!
- You know what? Let's just sleep.
We have a mission tomorrow, right?
- Let's take a rest now.
- [Ame] Come on, Mom!
- [Ame] Fix your hair first.
- Let's go.
[Ame] Oh, it's on the floor now.
- Let's go, let's go.
- [Ame] It reached here. [giggles]
[upbeat music playing]
[music fades]
[sinister music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
[in English] Uh, excuse me.
[in English] Can you tell me the way
to the rondalla performance at 6:30 p.m.?
[chuckles] Buenas noches!
Noches buenas!
[in Spanish] That's great.
You speak Spanish?
[in English] Uh, no, señora.
[in English] We don't really
speak Spanish fluently.
[in English] Yes, uh…
[in English] Only Spanish words
I know, uh…
[in English] Spanish bread.
[in English] Uh, Spanish sardines.
Hola! Señora.
Cuchara, atchara.
Maribeth Bichara.
Sayonara.
[in English] Uh, anyway, just go down,
and then turn right.
[in English] Then, just follow the signs
of the rondalla performance.
- Gracias!
- [Emerson, in English] Yes.
[in English] It means thank you.
Gracias dos.
[in English] Thank you too.
[sneaky music playing]
This is so hard, isn't it?
Turns out when you're in disguise,
you also need to know the language.
Why did you even speak Spanish?
Eh, eh…
We're civil guards, right?
It should be Spanish.
Brother Emerson, next time,
let's just stick to English.
That's the international language anyway.
Come on. I was just trying.
And don't call me Brother Emerson here.
Thread 1, okay?
Adopted Thread, don't forget.
We're here for OKA.
[in English] Operation Kidnap AFAM.
All right. Go back to your post.
Go back to your post.
Go.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
Uh, Thread 1.
[Emerson, in English] Hi, everybody.
How are your positions? Over.
This is itchy.
[in English] This is Thread 2, reporting.
I'm itching in this gown.
- I don't think I can dance later.
- [clears throat]
Karla.
That's called traje de mestiza.
Like what Maria Clara wore.
Brother Kurt, it's the same.
It's still itchy.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
- [in English] Hello!
- Hola!
Can we take a picture with you?
Of course! With a small fee.
- Joke only, guys.
- [camera shutter snaps]
- [in English] Thank you!
- [in English] Thank you.
Hey, it's Maria Clara!
Hola! Buenas noches!
- Can we take a picture with you?
- [in English] Of course!
[in Spanish] Thank you.
Uh, you're really…
You're really taking pictures there, huh.
- [chuckles softly]
- [music fades]
And this is the end of our tour.
Thank you for coming.
There's also a version in Bataan.
That's the original. Hope you can visit.
- [in English] Thank you! Bye!
- [in English] Thank you!
- [in English] Thank you.
- Thank you.
[sneaky music playing]
How's your location, Mini Thread?
It's fun.
I hope we can come here again,
but not on a mission,
but to stroll around.
Sis, are you talking to someone?
Oh, I'm just self-talking.
It's a trend.
Don't you do that?
[scoffs]
- [music fades]
- Ma'am, buy this, ma'am.
Puppet, ma'am!
It's very affordable, ma'am!
Do your best to sell there, Tape Measure.
But don't sell them all.
Leave one for me,
so I can give it to Ibyang
when we see each other.
[in English] Roger that.
Ma'am, buy this, ma'am!
Nine hundred… Oh, here! Just 500, ma'am.
Ma'am, sir, buy this puppet!
They're beautiful!
Mommy, Daddy, I want this.
You want it? It's very pretty!
I want that, please!
How much for that?
It used to be 1,200,
but I'll give it to you for 900.
This one was 700,
but just 500, sir, for baby.
Okay, we'll take it. Nine hundred.
- [Uno] Really? Okay.
- [kid] Yay!
Just be careful. It tangles.
But it still dances, look.
Like this. See?
[in English] Sir.
- Thank you, sir. Here's your change, sir.
- Thank you, brother.
And you were really able
to sell, Tape Measure.
[in English] Yes.
I can really sell, Thread 2.
- [sneaky music playing]
- The view here is beautiful.
You get it?
Huh?
Hey, Feeling Thread.
Can we focus on work?
"Feeling Thread"?
I am focused on work.
And there's no Feeling Thread here.
FYI. I meant you.
Ah.
My codename is Tape Measure.
[in English] Stick to that.
You're Feeling Thread to me.
You…
Stop it, stop it.
What's wrong with you?
Adopted Thread is right.
We need to focus.
We're here for…
Operation Kidnap AFAM.
So, how's it?
Have you found the location
of Tailor AFAM?
- Not yet.
- [in English] Negative.
No.
Okay, just…
update me when you see him.
Thanks.
- Thank you.
- [in English] Copy.
- [in English] Okay.
[in English] Roger that.
[in English] Yes, ma'am!
[music ends]
Brother Emerson, did you buy pepper spray?
Uh…
Just pepper.
[Emerson] Mmm, no spray.
That's fine.
Samir will still get teary-eyed from that.
[sneaky music playing]
So, what if Samir doesn't come here?
What if he suddenly decides
to go to Boracay?
It's already late,
and they're still not here.
What's with you?
You're so negative.
Don't be loud. You're the only one
I'll tell this to, okay.
I dreamt of Atoy again.
Yes. He told me I did very well.
I did a good job organizing this…
our operation, the Children of the Thread.
That's why I'm really confident
we will definitely find…
[suave theme music playing]
Tailor AFAM!
Attention, Children of the Thread.
Tailor AFAM has arrived with his family.
Thread 2 and Thread 3,
he's near your location,
so, get ready. Over.
[music fades]
[traditional instrumental music playing]
Hola! Buenas noches!
[ominous music playing]
[in Russian] My son, won't you tell me
where you got that scar on your face?
[in Russian] Did you get in trouble?
[in English] Have you been in trouble?
Samir is a mama's boy.
[Kurt sniffles]
I just remembered my own mother.
[in Russian] Mama,
can you stop doing that.?
[in Russian] You're embarrassing me.
[in English] You're sweating
in this lovely hour of the night!
[in English] A mother
cannot take care of her son?
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[sighs]
[suspicious music playing]
- [Lily grunts]
- Get ready.
But how, Atoy?
The lock is on the other side.
We can't reach it.
And we don't have anything to use here.
[Atoy] When they deliver the food,
they'll open the door.
That's when we'll do it.
[tense music playing]
Where's the bone?
[strains] Where's the bone?
[Atoy] Give it to me.
[Lily grunts]
- [lock rattles]
- [gasping]
- [music fades]
- [groans]
[henchman 1] You two.
You'll surely like this.
[ominous music playing]
What's this?
This isn't food.
[henchman 1] Soil!
Didn't you enjoy your steak last night?
So now, you'll eat soil!
[tense music playing]
You, like you.
I would love to bury you underground.
Just give us the laptop!
[huffs]
[applauding]
[traditional instrumental music playing]
[in Russian] It's awful,
this place is boring!
[in English] Don't talk like that.
[in English] You should appreciate
different cultures.
- [music fades]
- Olé!
[cheering, applauding]
[traditional instrumental music playing]
Damn it!
[sneaky music playing]
There's another sleazebag.
Sleazebag? Who?
A sleazebag indeed.
[music fades]
[henchman 1, in English] I'll go.
[ominous music playing]
[henchman 2, in English] Eat!
I told you!
[Lily, in English] No, no, no, no, no!
- [in English] Stop! No! Stop!
- [in English] Eat!
[Lily gasps]
[in English] You want?
- [Lily, in English] No, no.
- [in English] You too! Eat!
[mumbles]
[Lily, in English] No, no, no!
- [music swells]
- [grunts]
[grunts]
[Lily panting]
[Lily gasps]
[Lily gasping]
- [tense music playing]
- Let's go.
[in English] Okay. One, two, three, smile.
- [in English] Yes, smile!
- [camera shutter snaps]
[chuckles] Mabuhay!
[Kurt, in English] Wonderful.
- [in English] You're so cute!
- Oh!
[in English] Thank you so much. Oh!
[in English] Oh, sorry!
[sneaky music playing]
How are you? Buenas noches!
[Karla titters]
- [Samir, in English] What is your name?
- [in English] Uh, Kurt.
[clears throat, coughs]
Teous.
[in English] Uh,
very courteous staff here.
[Kurt, in English] I am Andrei Sokolov.
[in English] We are the Sokolov brothers.
[in English] You look familiar.
[in English] Oh, really?
[in English] You know,
I actually get that a lot.
[in English] They, uh… [chuckles]
[in English] They say I look like
a famous actor here in the Philippines.
[titters]
Uh, no, uh…
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Are you sure
you're not from Zahran?
[in English] Maybe you are Sokolov?
So-- Uh, Soko--
Sokol--
- [Samir] Sokolov.
- Sokolo--
- [in English] What?
- There.
[in English] Soko what?
No. I'm… I'm American, you know.
[in English] But Filipino at heart.
- [in English] No. You don't know him.
- [mom, in English] No, no, no, no.
[in English] Yes. He's American.
We're both American.
- Mmm-hmm.
- [in English] We just work here.
- [in English] Very American. Yes.
- [in English] Yes.
[in English] You look like
a business partner,
- Sokolov.
- [chuckles]
[in English] Okay.
[tense music playing]
[henchman] Where are you?
- [music fades]
- My boss isn't here.
Only Chiro and the captives are with me,
so we can drink all night.
[tense music playing]
We really need to get out of here
before more of them arrive.
- [softly] Come.
- [music fades]
- [in English] Let's go.
- [mom, in English] No, I don't think…
- [in English] Come on, Mother. Come on.
- [in English] He's so American.
- [Samir, in English] Let's go.
- [in English] Yes. Thank you.
[in English] Oh, madam! Uh, gentlemen, um,
would you guys like a private tour?
[in English] I could take you
to the heritage houses,
like Casa Monroy.
[in English] I would love to escort you.
[in English] Uh, it's
a very nice suggestion,
but, uh, we have to go.
[in English] It's eight o'clock.
We have dinner. I have work to do.
- [in English] Okay? Come on, let's go.
- [in English] Hedeon, please?
[in English] But brother,
could we stay a little longer?
[in English] I want to explore more
about the beauty of this place.
[in English] I agree. Let's go.
[in English] Follow me.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
The child of Thread 2 is on the move.
Let's go, to the next location.
Hurry.
Mini Thread is on the way.
[Charmi] Oh! It's beautiful.
It's so beautiful, Sister Faye.
- Hmm.
- I wish we could always come here.
If Mama Olga treats us
to places like this, why not?
Ibyang!
- [Ame] Ibyang!
- Sister Ame?!
- Hey!
[sentimental music playing]
- [electronic blipping]
- [music fades]
[tense music playing]
[cackles, in English] Surprise!
[in English] I will kill you.
[grunts]
[in English] Where is my brother?!
UP NEXT
Don't let the captives out!
[gunshots]
[Lily gasps]
[grunting]
[grunting and groaning]
[Kurt mumbles]
- [Lily, indistinct]
- [gunshots]
♪ Oh, Mr.Tailor, holding the scissors ♪
- [thug] Let's go!
- [Lily] Ouch!
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
‪Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias